Okay, so you may be wondering why on
earth do we spend that much time talking
about text and numbers? Well, to answer
your question, here are some things you
can do with it. Um, everything that you
do on the internet is a string.
Everything. So when you visit YouTube
and it pulls back the HTML page, that's
a string. If you know how to manipulate
strings, you can manipulate how that
works. Um,
I had an internship. They said, "Hey, we
need you to update these 100 HTML
pages." And I noticed that there was a
pattern with how they wanted me to
implement that. So, I wrote some string
manipulation and I ran my program and
six minutes later, all 100 pages were
updated. So, if you too like to be
faster at how you navigate the internet
and have superpowers, then string
manipulation is something you'll want to
be really good at. Um, and then the
other reason that we spent so long on
numbers is because just about everything
you work with is a number. Um, if you
are programming a financial system,
financial systems working with numbers.
If you are programming something that
allows people to schedule things on
their calendar, numbers. If you are
programming a shopping list, there are
probably numbers involved with that. So,
you really needed to be good at working
with both strings and numbers because in
almost everything you do, you will be
working with strings and numbers. So,
hopefully that explains why we spent so
long on that. We are now about to get
into the really exciting stuff and we
are going to talk about selection and it
just goes uphill from here. Everything
is so much fun from fun from here.
decided to get into it with